Selim Maurice Franklin papers, 1873-1931
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Professional Papers, 1873-1927
  - Property Case Files, 1886-1931
    - Tucson Property: Brown vs. Woodell, Lot 12, Block 92. 1903-1910 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Tucson Property: L. Goldschmidt vs. L. Roca, et al, Lots 10 & 11, Block 93. 1909-1921 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Tucson Property: L. Goldschmidt vs. C. Hoff, et al, various blocks. 1911-1913 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Tucson Property: Deed to R. V. Bloxton, Lots 3 & 6, Block 92. April 21, 1894 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Deed to G. Hoff, Lots 1-3, 11, & 12, Block 23. May 20, 1898 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Hazzard & Orfila vs. Tucson Gas, Electric Light & Power, Co. 1903 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: E. W. Graves, et al, vs. City of Tucson. 1906 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: A. Franklin vs. Cranston, Lot 17, Block 16. 1907 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Agreement between Highland Park CO. and Franklin & Heighton. March 23, 1907 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: A. V. Grossetta Contract with specifications for a house on 2nd St. 1912? (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Bills and receipts for a "new building, E. Congress St." 1913 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Agreement between B. Robles & T. Smith. 1913-1914 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Property: Hansen vs. Heidel, et al, Lot 6, Block 130. 1914 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Ocean Park, California. 1903-1910 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Avalon, Catalina Island, California. 1920-1926 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - La Jolla, California. 1916-1921 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Hermosa Beach, California. 1916 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - B. Robles vs. J. Kurtz, et al, Lot 9, Section 14, Township 14. 1914 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Callihan vs. Monier, irrigation ditch, Section 14, Township 14. 1907-1910 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Ft. Lowell irrigation ditch. 1897-1903 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Franklin & Heighton vs. C. Lincoln, Section 24, Township 13. 1912 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - M. Leon, et al vs. T. Benson, Lot 17, Section 11, Township 14. 1909-1910 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Deed to J. B. Salpointe by President McKinley, Lot 21, Section 14, Township 14. May 20, 1897 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Deed, Kaphan to Balcom, Section 31, Township 20. 1906 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - U. S. vs. J. Wise, Township 21-22. 1903 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - J. Brash vs. S. Parke, irrigation ditch, Section 8, Township 22. 1906 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Personal property: taxes, insurance, repairs. 1889-1925 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 135 E. Congress, Woods and Handley (tobacco, newspapers, magazines). 1911-1912 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 135 E. Congress, Briggs & Handley (tobacco, newspapers, magazines). 1916-1917 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 135 E. Congress Handley & Sandlin (tobacco, newspapers, magazines). 1918-1919 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 202 E. Congress, J. C. Penney Co. 1920-1921 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 202 E. Congress, Drs. Schell & Schell (optometrists & opticians). 1924-1926 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 216 E. Congress, People's Market. 1916-1917 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 216 E. Congress, E. G. Capo (jeweler). 1917-1927 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 216 E. Congress, incomplete lease. 1931 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 234 E. Congress, S P Grocery. 1921 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 240 E. Congress, T. A. Ring (photo supplies). 1917 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 240 E. Congress, Sucursal de Calderon Hermanos (music store). 1918 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 240 E. Congress, E. B. Moore Oil Investments Co. 1919-1920 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 240 E. Congress, New York Cleaning Works (C. D. Churchill). 1926-1927 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 250 E. Congress, M. Rosen (tailor). 1917-1918 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 250 E. Congress, McDonald's Kitchen. 1926 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 250 E. Congress, Star Grill. 1926-1927, 1931 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 260 E. Congress, Economy Shoe Store (J. H. Vermilyea). 1918-1919 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for Puhl Bros. Fancy Grocery. 1926 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for Congress & 6th Ave, Tucson Warehouse & Transfer Co. 1909-1911 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for Congress & 6th Ave., W. Goldring & Sons, Inc.. (furniture, stoves, etc.). 1917-1919 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for ?? E. Congress, ABC Root Beer Stand. 1926-1927 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 221 E. Broadway, Snow & Tufts Auto Co. 1924-1925 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 221 E. Broadway, Gibbs Motor Co. 1926 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 31-33 S. 6th Ave., Roberts & Reynolds Garage. 1917-1919, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 31-33 S. 6th Ave., Fred C. Roberts Garage. 1926-1927 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Franklin & Heighton Rental Collection Reports for 142 N. 6th Ave, Mrs. Ella Simpson (residence). 1923-1924 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Utility bills, water. 1921-1924 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Utility bills, telephone, gas and light. 1921-1925 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding property, land, mortgages, etc. 1886-1926 (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
      Includes letters relating to desert land entries; property in Casa Grande, Crittenden, Nogales, San Diego, Santa Cruz Valley, Malibu Ranch in California; sale of the San Pedro Ranch.
  - Miscellaneous Case Files, 1880-1926
    - Tax Case: Tucson Natatorium. 1909-1913 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Tax Case: S. Franklin vs. Tucson Opera House Co. 1880-1898 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Tax Case: Chillson & Hoff, Block 30, Tucson. 1891-1906 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Tax Case: Miscellaneous material relating to Blocks 30 & 49, Tucson. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Tax Cases: Various. 1902-1920 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      Chiefly involving the Arizona National Bank of Tucson and the Consolidated National Bank.
    - Debt Case: Ramirez vs. Main. 1903-1908 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Debt Case: S. Franklin vs. F. Proctor. 1903 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: C. Gooding vs. J. McDonald, et al. 1903-1904 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: Charter Gas Engine Co. vs. Gardiner, Worthen & Goss Co. 1904-1907 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: L. Goldschmidt vs. W. Campbell. 1904-1910 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: Phillips, Drew & Co. vs. G. Ruez. 1907-1908 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: Tucson Printing & Publishing Co. vs. C. Hoff. 1910 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: J. M Ormsby vs. C. Bolen. 1911-1913 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: Eagle Milling Co. vs. W. Layne. 1914-1915 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: B. Robles vs. B. Rosenfeld. 1915 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Debt Case: C. Phillips vs. L. B. Young. No date (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Mortgage Case: Bigger vs. Ochoa. 1889-1895 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Mortgage Case: Maricopa Loan & Trust Co. vs. C. Drake. 1893-1897 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: H. O'Sullivan vs. J. de Elias, et al. 1904 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: B. M. Jacobs vs. J. Mallen de Moreno, et al. 1905-1910 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: George Berkalew Mortgages. 1906, 1911 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: Nogales Building & Loan vs. E. Griswold, et al. 1909-1910 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: B. M. Jacobs vs. V. Almenar. 1912 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: F. Gustetter vs. A. Gustetter. 1912 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage Case: A. M. Franklin vs. V. Almenar. 1912-1913 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: L. Pascholy vs. J. Pascholy. 1903-1914 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: R. Hopkins, adoption by G. & A. Johnson. 1905 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: M. Stevens vs. C. Stevens. 1905 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: F. Clancy vs. J. Clancy. 1905-1906 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: Josephine B. Martin Case. 1905-1908 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: G. Avery vs. C. Avery. 1909 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: A. Saenz, guardian of C. & Y. Saenz. 1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Case: J. Toumey, guardianship. 1914 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence: Divorce and/or Domestic Relations Cases. 1887-1919 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Bankruptcy: H. Blaisdell. 1899-1901 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Bankruptcy: Aston and Maloney. 1902-1904 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Bankruptcy: Heermans Stationery Co. 1903-1904 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Bankruptcy: McCourt & Geddes. 1903-1904 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Bankruptcy: Estate of W. S. Felix. 1904 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Bankruptcy: Gardiner, Worthen & Goss Co. 1908-1909 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Business Establishments: Arizona Brewing Co. 1908-1909 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Business Establishments: Arizona May-Oatway Fire Alarms, Inc. 1912-1914 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Business Establishments: Atlantic & Pacific Oil Company. 1901-1902 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Business Establishments: Brena Commercial Company. 1900-1903 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Business Establishments: Concrete Construction Company. 1913-1914 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Business Establishments: Eagle Milling Company. 1913, 1919 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: East Congress Street Building Company. 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: El Prado Improvement Company. 1916-1924 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Eldorado State Company. 1916-1923 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Fleishman's Drug Store. 1911 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Gila Valley Milling Company. 1911-1921 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Guaranteed Investments Corporation of America. 1912 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Guardian Investment Company. 1916-1917 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Mesa Co-operative Milling Company. 1909-1912 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Business Establishments: Norton-Morgan Commercial Company. 1903 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Business Establishments: Phillips, Drew & Company. 1907 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Business Establishments: Rule & Sons, Inc. 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Business Establishments: Tucson Pressed Brick Company. 1908-1917 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Business Establishments: Wooding Train Controls. 1917-1925 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Building and Loan Association. 1898-1926 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Hebrew Benevolent Society. 1886-1913 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - International Commercial Co. 1913 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Santa Cruz Water Storage Co. 1892-1894 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - West Side Improve Co.: Correspondence, Legal Papers, etc. 1909-1913 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - West Side Improve Co.: Stock Book. (Box 66)
    - International Bank in Nogales vs. National Mexican Mining Co. 1898-1900 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - International Bank in Nogales: Correspondence. 1904-1911 (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
    - Dessart vs. International Bank in Nogales. 1904-1910 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - International Bank in Nogales: Herrera vs. Lewis. 1904-1908 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - International Bank in Nogales: Various legal cases chiefly involving Herrera, Receiver of the Bank. 1904-1905 (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
    - First National Bank of Nogales: Various legal cases. 1908-1921 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      Includes suits against the Bank by E. Pope, Pastene & Co., Ensenada Tanning Co., and Henry Cohen.
    - Utility: Bisbee Light and Power Co., legal case of W. H. Goode. 1908-1909 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Utility: Douglas Gas Corporation, legal Case with City of Douglas. 1909-1910 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Utility: Nogales Electric Light, Ice & Water Co. 1915-1919 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Utility: Nogales Gas Co., correspondence. 1910-1923 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Utility: L. Ephraim vs. Nogales Gas Co. 1909-1911? (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Utility: Nogales Gas Co., J. Moore vs. W. Chenoweth, et al. 1910-1911 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Utility: Nogales Water Co., correspondence and legal cases. 1901-1912 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Utility: Nogales Water Co., miscellaneous papers, clippings, ordinances and legal papers. 1904-1912 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Utility: Tucson Electric Light and Power Co. 1901-1903 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Utility: Tucson Water Works. 1891-1898 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Utility: Yuma Water and Light Co., suits of Blaisdell Co. and Gargill, et al. 1905 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Utility: Yuma Electric and Water Co. 1911 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Citizens' Building & Loan Association of Tucson, Arizona: Miscellaneous material. 1908-1909, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Tucson Building & Loan Association of Tucson, Arizona: By-laws. 1888 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Citizens' Building & Loan Association of Tucson, Arizona vs. C. Leon, et al, regarding the Estate of J. B. Tenney. 1909-1912 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Citizens' Building & Loan Association of Tucson, Arizona vs. J. Zepeda, et al. 1910-1911 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Citizens' Building & Loan Association of Tucson, Arizona: Various legal cases. 1909-1924 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      Includes suits against:
      E. Van Kuren, et al
      M. Christy, et al
      J. Kurtz, et al
      A. Saenz, et al
      H. Blaise, et al
      B. Wood
    - Eduardo Ramirez Extradition Case: Legal papers. 1907-1908 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
    - Eduardo Ramirez Extradition Case: Correspondence, undated legal papers, miscellaneous material. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Indian Depredations: Ferguson vs. Estate of T. Hughes. 1888-1908 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Indian Depredations: Miscellaneous correspondence. 1892-1899 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Samaniego vs. Stiles. 1887-1890 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - "Globe Road Case," Pusch vs. California Bridge Co. and Pusch vs. Pinal County Bank. 1891-1895 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Gill vs. Minor. 1895-1896 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Dysart vs. Graham County. 1898-1900 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Ackerman vs. Kaufman. 1912-1913 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham vs. Fisher. 1886 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Various cases involving the Charouleau family. 1886-1898 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Noon vs. Steinfeld. 1886-1887 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Cases involving J. Mohan. 1886-1888 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Rogers vs. Goldman & Co. 1886-1888 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Various cases involving W. J. Tweed. 1886-1888 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Flood & Haskins vs. J. B. Raine. 1887-1891 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Martin vs. Wells Fargo & Co. 1887-1889 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Rosenberg vs. Melozer. 1887-1888 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Eccleston vs. Robinson. 1887-1889 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Hamlin vs. Southern pacific Co. 1888 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Giant Powder Co. vs. Anderson & Co. 1888 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Wells Fargo & Co. case. 1888-1889 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Sestier vs. Ephraim. 1888-1889 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Strauss vs. Cheyney. 1890-1891 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Lindley vs. Spencer. 1890-1898 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - J. Stephens vs. A. Hoover. 1891-1892 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - U. S. vs. S. H. Drachman. 1892, 1894 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Harrison vs. Doherty. 1893-1894 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - I. Levy vs. C. Alvarado. 1893-1894 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Steinfeld vs. Doran. 1893-1899 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Molina vs. Modesti. 1894-1895 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Gandolfo & Sanguinetti vs. Purdy, et al. 1894-1895 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Menager vs. Farrell. 1897-1899 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Dean & Forget vs. Paredes, Paredes vs. Fitts & McDonough. 1897-1899 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - A. Abbott vs. R. Williams. 1898-1899 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Wong Fook Ling vs. S.White & L. Zeckendorf & Co. 1898-1899 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Arizona National Bank of Tucson vs. A. Castaneda. 1903 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - J. Clancy vs. R. Millar. 1905 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - A. Rossi vs. C. Hoff. 1905-1906 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Will of N. Bernard, and Agreements with the Tucson Ice & Cold Storage Co. 1907 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - C. Minier vs. A. Moore & Citizen Print & Publishing Co. 1908-1910 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - A. Williams vs. Aetna Life Insurance Co. 1908 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - C. Ramirez vs. T. J. Turner, et al. 1909 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - B. Robles vs. J. Jacobs. 1912 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Tharp vs. Fidelity & Casualty Co.of New York. 1916 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - G. Gross vs. J. W. Smith. 1916-1917 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Consolidated National Bank vs. Kemp. 1917-1920 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Estate: Barnes, William H. 1904-1908 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Estate: Bowers, Edward W. 1902-1903 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Estate: Collins, J. B. 1885?-1890 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Estate: Davis, William C. 1889-1905 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Estate: Herring, Bertha. 1925-1926 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Estate: Herring, William. 1813-1916 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Estate: Horton, W. B. 1887-1889 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Estate: Inslee, Helen and Samuel. 1916-1925 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Jacobs, Belle. 1925-1926 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Johnson, Ada. 1900-1905 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Estate: Meade, Helen. 1911-1916 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Neville and Chapin: Probate Court. 1900-1905 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Neville and Chapin: Arizona State Supreme Court. 1904-1905? (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Neville and Chapin: U. S. District Court. 1904-1906 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      Case of O. K. Franklin, Administrator of the Estate of J. Neville vs. M. M. Trickey, Administrator of the Estate of N. H. Chapin, involving mining property.
    - Estate: Olsen, Annie. 1924-1926 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Estate: Olsen, Frederick. 1908-1913 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Estate: Pomeroy, Ellen (Nellie). 1921-1925 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Estate: Schramm, H. W. 1889 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Estate: Silva, Peter. 1887-1889 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Estate: Sorin, Sarah, H. 1914-1925 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Estate: Walker, John D. and Walker, Lucien. 1897-1896 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Estate: Austin, F. L. 1896 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Bauer, Charles. 1908 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Cameron, Brewster. 1909 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Cavelli, Paul. 1897-1898 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Chazet, Nicholas. 1897 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Cohn, Louis. 1890 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Duncan. R. J. 1902-1903 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Duvall, Louis. 1898-1899 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Elliott, Calvin A. 1912 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Fitzgerald, J. T. 1896-1900 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Florsheim, Gertrude. 1919-1920 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Girard, Louisa. 1905-1906 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Goldschmidt, Adolf. 1912 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Estate: Halbert, ?? 1898 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Hill, Tobias C. 1914 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Hudson, E. N. 1890-1892 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Hunter Alexander. 1902 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Jacobs, Hannah. 1886-1887 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Lamb, A. C. No date (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Leon, Ramona E. de. 1901-1902 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Lung So Wo. 1909 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Meyer, Charles. 1896-1897 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Moses (alias Zier), Max. 1888 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Murphey, Aletha. 1895 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Parsons, Robert B. 1905 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Pieront, Effie B. 1896 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Estate: Rebeil, Leonie. 1914 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      Also includes papers regarding the guardianship of Julia R. Charouleau.
    - Estate: Scott, Mrs. E. R. 1894-1896 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Estate: Stephens, John L. 1894-1895 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Estate: Tufts, Matthias R. 1912 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Estate: White, George E. 1899-1900 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Estate: Wormser, ?? 1900-1901 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Estate: Zepeda, Francesca B. 1910 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous estate correspondence. 1887-1896 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Claims and collections cases. 1886-1926 (Box 74, Folder 1-6)
    - Claims and collections case: Rogers vs. Encinas. 1886-1887 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: R. Robinson vs. Anderson. 1887-1893 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Stephens vs. Green. 1889-1892 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Childress, et al vs. J. T. Fitzgerald. 1891 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Fisk vs. Tebbets. 1897-1898 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Fraser & Chalmers vs. Gardiner, Worthen & Goss. 1897-1898 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Sutherland vs. Maldonado. 1898 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: H. Chapin vs. F. Russell. 1902 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Hoff Auto Co. vs. Studebaker Colorado Vehicle Co. 1909-1912 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Claims and collections case: Banco de Sonora vs. A. M. Moreno. 1910-1911 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Series III: Merrill P. Freeman Papers, 1878-1927
  - Correspondence: Selim M. Franklin. 1890-1918 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Cameron Family. 1890-1918 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: J. Edoff. 1900-1902 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous Family. 1899-1921 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: University of Arizona. 1894 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Mining: Mammoth-Collins Gold Mines, Ltd. 1896-1901 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Mining: Tres Amigos Gold Mines. 1900 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Mining: Miscellaneous. 1899-1917 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Political Correspondence including letters from Governor N. O. Murphy and Governor A. O. Brodie. 1897-1902 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Business and Banking Correspondence including a letter from Warrensburg, Mo. regarding an experiment in chemical rain-making. 1866-1916 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Herbert Brown and others regarding the sale of the Tucson Citizen. 1900-1901 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous personal correspondence. 1893-1902 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Death and Estate papers. 1919-1927 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Estate financial records. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Masonic Material. 1878-1902 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Post Office. 1880-1887 (Box 76, Folder 2-3)
- Series IV: Zeckendorf Family Papers, 1887-1911
  - Louis Zeckendorf: Correspondence. 1887-1901 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Louis Zeckendorf: Various legal cases. 1887-1911 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - A. H. Zeckendorf vs. Louis Zeckendorf. 1892-1901 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Hugo A. Zeckendorf Jewelry Co.: Correspondence. 1894-1901 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Hugo A. Zeckendorf Jewelry Co.: Cash Book. October 1894-July 1898 (Box 77, Folder 5)